[{
    "id": "FEA628A1-F39C-4DA3-AECD-3041823056A8",
    "question" : "abound in/with",
    "answer" : "(vrb.) exist in great numbers or amount."
},
{
    "id": "7C080F4A-5121-49E0-99F2-E7581E5153F9",
    "question" : "accost",
    "answer" : "(v.) to approach and speak to first / to confront in a challenging or aggressive way"
},
{
    "id": "7B428B27-D88F-4205-8C95-F6F66C39388E",
    "question" : "annals",
    "answer" : "(n.) a record of events year by year. / historical record"
},
{
    "id": "568CBE24-11E1-4CF3-9D3B-9CD82B324DFC",
    "question" : "automaton",
    "answer" : "(n.) a moving mechanical device made in imitation of a human being."
},
{
    "id": "71038D6F-73F8-41F0-8E7E-23D7267B698E",
    "question" : "badger",
    "answer" : "(v.) repeatedly ask someone to do something / to pester/ nag / annoy persistently."
},
{
    "id": "45BD4396-2D1D-4ECE-BDD9-7ECEE52C5259",
    "question" : "compound",
    "answer" : "(adj.) made up or consisting of two or more parts or elements. / (v.) mix or combine"
},
{
    "id": "F1D212FF-F9C4-4A80-8B77-ECE60F11FC94",
    "question" : "drudgery",
    "answer" : "(n.) dull work / unpleasant task"
},
{
    "id": "36ACF810-DF14-4A3A-AC97-E8014819904B",
    "question" : "eminent",
    "answer" : "(adj.) famous and respected."
},
{
    "id": "FE754A91-F648-4B1F-9F5C-7AC2FBA78FAC",
    "question" : "frame of reference",
    "answer" : "(n.) a particular set of beliefs or ideas on which you base your judgement of things."
},
{
    "id": "72FEFD34-5B80-47B0-8099-1C097E3427D9",
    "question" : "implore",
    "answer" : "(v.) beg someone earnestly or desperately to do something."
},
{
    "id": "1F303AE7-1F12-4584-8078-C2456ED9F74F",
    "question" : "indiscriminate",
    "answer" : "(adj.) acting without careful judgement."
},
{
    "id": "E7C11C8A-8F8C-44E7-94BE-2BD7B66C95C2",
    "question" : "interminable",
    "answer" : "(adj.) endless / having or seeming to have no end"
},
{
    "id": "27573E91-DBDE-46DA-825B-CAF5451B86AA",
    "question" : "intrepid",
    "answer" : "(adj.) very brave / fearless / unshakable"
},
{
    "id": "2143C362-D823-4D77-8C76-BF69EC9DD1D9",
    "question" : "laconic",
    "answer" : "(adj.) concise / using few words"
},
{
    "id": "CA321FA8-02E8-4A15-8623-0709CAC483BC",
    "question" : "matron",
    "answer" : "(n.) an older married woman."
},
{
    "id": "79248C2C-7E86-41EC-8FAF-F4538F34DA52",
    "question" : "paradox",
    "answer" : "(n.) a self-contradictory statement or proposition, that when investigated or explained, may prove to be well founded or true."
},
{
    "id": "FAE6583A-95D7-44B9-898A-3ABD91FE120A",
    "question" : "perceive",
    "answer" : "(v.) become aware / come to realize or understand"
},
{
    "id": "1101DB9C-B4A3-4CC5-A6A1-BC76F9693576",
    "question" : "prognosticate",
    "answer" : "(vrb.) to predict or tell the future."
},
{
    "id": "E1DD6446-13D4-4B55-BB85-E4C72C3A9E07",
    "question" : "realm",
    "answer" : "(n.) a field or domain of activity or interest"
},
{
    "id": "8C65DE39-7CB4-4080-8EA7-F54E68ECAE19",
    "question" : "replete",
    "answer" : "(adj.) filled or well supplied with something."
},
{
    "id": "CC4790BF-6A61-4138-825C-38327CC6F879",
    "question" : "reticent",
    "answer" : "(adj.) not revealing one's thoughts or feelings readily"
},
{
    "id": "FE866449-4261-4633-B7E5-94D00C0C844E",
    "question" : "steep",
    "answer" : "(adj.) spent a lot of time thinking or learning about something."
},
{
    "id": "21253C46-097B-4763-A0B8-13D247A2707C",
    "question" : "technology",
    "answer" : "(n.) machinery and equipment developed from the application of scientific knowledge."
},
{
    "id": "6E820CC0-3D7B-4593-B617-A9C6463D2A6E",
    "question" : "throng",
    "answer" : "(n.) a large gathering of people"
},
{
    "id": "6113CA34-5116-49A5-9DBF-5D0773E3B2D2",
    "question" : "tinge",
    "answer" : "(n.) a slight trace of feeling or quality. / (v.) imbue slightly with a feeling or quality."
},
{
    "id": "8B27F1A8-3671-4033-9612-5DABC1034450",
    "question" : "voracious",
    "answer" : "(adj.) having a huge appetite / greedy / ravenous / excessively eager."
}]
